All right. Hello everybody. Uh
good evening. Good evening. Good
evening. Um
I am
coming to you live from Virginia.
Um,
just gonna wait a few moments for uh for
everybody to jump on. And um, first of
all, I want to thank you guys. For those
of you that have been praying for my
father, thank you very much. Um,
the prayers are definitely appreciated.
Um, please continue to lift him in
prayer and um, just that the Lord's will
will be done uh, for him. Um,
so guys, tonight I want to just uh talk
to you for a few moments about the uh
Daniel in seven days course that I'm
going to be teaching
um starting this Sunday night. So that's
December
uh 7th.
Uh sorry about that. I'm going to put
this on silence here. So, um December
7th, we will be doing our next Daniel in
7 days course. Um and that's going to be
followed um by the Revelation in 7 days
course. Um
this is an intensive
7 days,
14 hours of training. Uh first on the
book of Daniel, then on the book of
Revelation. Uh we're going to be going
into great depth for those that have
taken the class already. Um they have
had a very powerful experience
um gaining a deeper understanding of
both the books of Daniel and Revelation.
Just let me mention that you do not need
to take both classes. They they are
separate classes. So if you want to take
both that's fine. If you just want to
focus on one Daniel or Revelation that
is fine as well. Um, so I'm going just
share a little bit a little bit um about
my journey you guys with the book books
of Daniel and Revelation and um just
some of the things that I
um experienced as I was studying these
books coming into the church and being
new and kind of like you know getting my
hands on the writings of the pioneers
and uh really getting down into the
books of Daniel and Revelation. And I
will just say this that one of the one
of the main
um
questions I had when I would read our
commentaries on the books of Daniel and
Revelation um was first of all I was
like man that's powerful like this this
understanding of the prophecy makes
sense but the thing that I did not
understand was how did you come to that
conclusion right so I would see
different explan explanations like an
explanation about the the seven churches
and about the seven seals and about the
seven trumpets and I just asked myself
well how did they come to this
conclusion right and I don't know if you
all have ever had that experience where
you may be reading one of uh one of our
books on prophecy and um and you get
what is being said but if someone asks
you well why this interpretation you
probably be left like with a blank stare
right like well I don't know but I read
it in the book and I believe
Um, that was an issue for me. Uh, I
wanted to know if I was going to be
teaching. Um, and you guys excuse the
noise. I'm I'm not in my home
environment. I'm in my home environment,
but not in my home environment. So, um,
if you hear noise in the background,
just, uh, lock in.
So, [clears throat] um, I would read
these these, uh, these books again and
I'd say, ' Man, this understanding is is
I get it. But if someone were to ask me,
"Hey, pastor, how do you why is this why
are the seven trumpets to be understood
this way versus that way?" I would have
struggled
to give an answer um as to why a
prophecy should be viewing should be
viewed one way over another.
So over the years, the question that I
wanted to ask myself, the question that
I asked myself was, look, if I was to
teach this book to someone who didn't
know anything about the book, and
they're asking me questions like, well,
why is this so why is it like this here,
but not like this here, right? Why is
why the seven churches represent this?
Why are the seven seals covering this
time period and they're not in the
future or they're not all in the past?
How do you answer those questions? That
was my baseline
for studying the books of Daniel and
Revelation. In other words, I didn't
just want to know the what, but I wanted
to know the why.
And that's what I will be teaching um
and have been teaching in the Daniel in
seven days, the Revelation in Seven Days
courses is I'm not just saying to you,
hey, this is what the seven trumpets
are. This is what the the the uh this is
who the four beasts are in Daniel
chapter 7. And this is who the little
horn is in Daniel chapter 7 and 8. I'm
not just telling you why it's not anti
antiacus epiphies. I'm showing you I'm
not just telling you that it's not
Antiochus Epiphanies. I'm showing you
why. Right? And that's a pretty big one,
the little horn of Daniel 8. But when
we're looking at why is the book of
Daniel written in in a format that
allows us to be able to begin to fill in
the blanks with certainty?
Are there principles behind the study of
the book of Daniel? Are there principles
behind the the study of the book of
Revelation? Are there patterns that are
seen in these books that help us to know
well it has to be this and it cannot be
this? I believe that once you understand
the the the structures of these books,
the why becomes
a pretty powerful study, right? So
again, if you have taken a Daniel and
Revelation course before, maybe the
course was a month long, maybe it was,
you know, a couple of months long, uh,
an entire series, and you've walked away
going, "Okay,
but I I still don't think I could teach
that or even explain it back to someone
well enough. It's just too much
information."
If you want to be able to approach the
book of Daniel in a way that
will remain locked in your mind, in a
way that that you may not be a teacher
of prophecy, but if you were asked,
well, why is this this way and not this
way? You'd be able to answer it. You'd
be able to explain the why and not just
the what.
um this 7-day course in Daniel and in
Revelation, it is for you.
So guys, um we've got three days left
until this uh um Daniel in 7 days
starts. It's going to be starting
Sunday. It is again 7 days, two hours
each day, two hours per day of teaching.
This is not going to be fluff teaching.
This is not going to be a fill-in-
thelank. Okay. So, Babylon meet a pers
of Greece Rome. We're going to be
dealing with with principles with
patterns that are going to help you to
better understand these books um to the
point where you will be able to explain
it to someone else with a with a with a
little practice, right? With a little
training, with a little more studying,
um you will be at a place where you can
explain these prophecies
confidently.
Confidently.
So with that said guys, I am going to um
put the link in the chat here. Um
in fact,
yeah, I'm just going to go ahead and
copy and paste this. So uh here is the
link to the chat, I mean to the to the
uh registration page.
Um,
all right. There you go.
Um, okay. And if you have any questions,
um, please feel free to email me, okay?
A burninghammergmail.com.
A burninghammer@gmail.com.
Um, or you can just email me through the
site. I will get the the email through
the site as well through the photo uh
the myphototheology
uh.com website. All right, guys. So,
that's it. I look forward uh to seeing
you in class starting this Sunday, 700
p.m. uh Central Standard Time. And by
the way, if you're unable to make any
class, it's all going to be recorded.
So, you will have uh lifetime access to
the recordings. Um, so you don't need to
worry about, hey, I don't know if I'll
be able to make it this day or that day
or any of these days because the whole
class will be recorded. Okay? So, for
those for those that sign up for the
class, you're going to have access to
the class, lifetime access to the class
and and the and the videos and the PDFs.
Okay? All right, guys. That's it. I'm
going to go ahead and sign off. Uh,
yeah, put a one in the chat if you got
that.
And uh you guys be blessed and uh I will
see you uh by God's grace in class. All
right. Blessings.